I feel like I fit in with someone I have a crush on.
Looks delicious, soooo
It's sweet.
A little sweet.
Huh?
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Hi! Hello! I'm Marie Morimoto!
Yes, well, I'm going to eat shaved ice today!
I'm going to eat shaved ice!
And the place I'm visiting this time is Shichijoji Temple!
The restaurant we are going to today is one that I have had my eye on for a long, long time.
I've been wanting to go there for a long time now.
But yes, that's why I have a non-qualified license to visit today.
I don't know what to do, I'm so happy!
I'm so excited!
Wait a minute!
I'm quite embarrassed.
I feel like a YouTuber.
I am a YouTuber.
I'm walking.
This is my first time in Kichijoji,
Oh! It's windy!
Shaved ice on a windy day of all days!
I'm okay. I'm fine.
I'm the one who went out for shaved ice on a day when there was a warning of heavy rain
I went out to eat shaved ice on a day when there was a warning of heavy rain.
I can stand this wind.
I'll turn!
I haven't had shaved ice for about a week.
I eat shaved ice about 3 times a week.
I haven't had shaved ice for a week.
So I'm looking forward to it!
I'm more excited than happy! I'm more excited than happy!
Morimoto
Is it this way?
Excuse me
Raise your hand and you'll get it.
I'm so nervous to be followed. What should I do?
What should I do?
What should I do? I feel like I'm meeting someone I have a crush on.
Oops!
Here we are!
Is this good?
We're here!
This way!
It's the ice shop Pi-stan!
Wow!
I'm so happy! I've never been here before!
Can you see it? The letters on the ice
Ice.
I'm so happy!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God! I'm so happy!
Ha!
Excuse me!
Hello!
This way!
The outside table.
I'm outside!
I'm so happy!
I've never had shaved ice at Trusty's before.
I've never had shaved ice at Trasteki before.
I feel a bit nervous about it.
It's going to be winter now.
Oh, hello!
Hello!
Menu.
What?
The one I've been after.
American Chili Rare Cheese
I'm so happy! Yes, we have it!
What's lubber milk?
I was just wondering.
Cherry Brulee?
Estragon-scented cherry brulee.
What? What is it?
Cherry Brulee?
Excuse me!
And then...
American chili rare cheese.
American chili rare cheese?
Yes, thank you!
Thank you very much!
Ice.
Since I've been into shaved ice.
I've come across a lot of words
I've come across many words I've never heard before.
Like rhubarb.
What? I don't know.
Do you know what rhubarb is?
Do you hear it in everyday life? Rhubarb.
Rhubarb...
I'm looking forward to it.
I really like shaved ice with cherry blossoms.
I'm so happy!
I'm wearing short sleeves right now, but I forgot my jacket today, and I'm starting to get worried.
I wonder if it'll get coldI hope it doesn't get cold.
I once went to eat there in the middle of winter and got a stomach ache.
I had to drive to Makuhari for a music show at that time.
Thank you very much.
Let me take a picture.
It looks so good, it's melting, it's melting, it's melting.
It looks delicious. Look at this.
It's even more pink-pink than I thought it would be.
Excuse me, I've got some shaved ice here, but it's always 3 days before I can take a picture of it.
Hold this.
Live, live, live, live!
Three days!
It's so beautiful!
Bon appétit! Can I eat it now, it's melting?
Bon appétit! I'll have some.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious! Wait a minute.
I'm so lucky.
I'll just have it here.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Wow!
Delicious.
She is too much more cheese biased than I thought she would be.
You can feel the pulp of the cherries from the cheese alone.
That's what she is, cherries.
Wow, very tasty.
I meant to say that when I appeared, too delicious, I would be like a refusal.
Sorry.
They are soooo delicious.
They look delicious.
Happy.
It's sweet.
It's still a little... eh?
Mmm-hmm.
Big deal.
I just had a gory happening, didn't I?
It's gone.
It's gone no matter how long I keep trying to eat it.
It's pretty much my favorite Hachiori I've had in 3 months.
It's really a great type.
Hmmm...
You see that giree on the top?
I'm going to put this on the bottom of the Hachiori.
I've been wanting to eat the same amount of it together.
I want to eat it in the same proportions.
I always have a hard time with that.
I want to be good at it.
When I get good at it, I want to be happy all the time, all the way to the end.
Hmm...
I often go out for shaved ice with Haruyo Yamaguchi.
Whenever I say where I want to go, Haruyo usually comes with me.
But Haruyo also brings me a lot of shaved ice.
Pistachio together!
Harion and I have a lot in common that we both like pistachios.
I'm going to try the pistachio!
Hmmm!
I'm getting sad to finish it.
I'm getting sad to finish eating them.
My legs are concentrating now.
It's going into hyper-concentration mode.
Is that the sound of grinding?
Where are they grinding?
Oh!
There's a little bit left!
Hmmm...
Mmm!
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Thank you for the food!
It was delicious!
It was my first time to go to Coryapece.
It was really delicious!
It's my type of restaurant!
Okay, I'll see you then.
Well, here it is!
Look at this!
Cafe Fumiel!
Here we are!
Shaved ice shop!
He's so handsome!
If you go to a shaved ice shop, you can have two or more!
Now let's go in!
I'm really, really far back.
I'm so nervous!
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Excuse me, I'm going.
Excuse me. Hello. Excuse me, please.
Excuse me. I'd like to take this seat.
It's so beautiful, it's really, really pretty.
It's so cute! It's like something out of a fairy tale.
Let's take a look at the shaved ice menu.Let's take a quick look at the shaved ice menu!
Ta-da! Oh! This is the one you see so often, isn't it?
Lumiere's baked ice!
And this one? Oh, this tastes like shaved ice without the baking!
Oh, wow! Look! I found it here! Oh, my God, I'm in love with this chili pie.
Oh, I'm in love. I'm in love. I'm so in love. I'm also interested in the chocolate mint parfait.
Choco mint parfait is the most popular one.
I'll have the chocolate mint parfait, please.
I'm having a hard time deciding between the chili pie and the chili pie, but I'll have two cups of the chocolate mint parfait.
I'm satisfied with one bowl, but I want to eat a little more.
So I'm happy to have two bowls today, too.
Oh, wait a minute, I feel like I've fallen off the wagon.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I see it!
I got it.
Here you go.
Chocolate Mint Palmier Carré.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious!
Mint!
Here is the chocolate mint mint syrup.
Mint syrup?
Thank you very much.
Here it comes!
Wow!
It smells great!
It smells like chocolate mint.
It's already big.
As you can see from below.
It's a really beautiful color.
I don't know what to do, I hope it doesn't fall apart too much this time.
Bon appétit!
First time eating! Looks delicious!
Mmm!
Wow! It's mint!
Refreshing mint!
But...
Wow! Quite a bit of chocolate
The chocolate sauce is quite rich.
It goes really well with
with this refreshing mint.
Wow! It's too good!
This chocolate mint dessert is so good!
It's too good!
This is too good.
Oh, my God!
Wait a minute, I'm surprised it's so early in the game.
Mmm-mmm-mmm!
Look at the layers of mint sauce on the inside!
It's crispy, and then the chocolate comes out.
Oh, wow!
Delicious!
Yum!
I love the different textures, it's so good!
Here's what I really like about it.
The outside is covered with so much cream.
I thought it was really nice that even if it melts, it doesn't drip down to the outside.
It might be good for people who are not used to eating shaved ice!
I highly recommend it!
It's delicious!
You should eat this side because it's dangerous!
Let's put a little bit here inside.
Mmmm...
This is delicious!
I did it again.
Wait a minute. I did it again. I did it again.
Done it again.
I better not do anything weird.
Yum!
I was trying to eat evenly.
I couldn't do that.
I...
Wait a minute, this is really bad.
It's just so visually beautiful.
I'm a terrible eater.
I'd like to put some of the wint sauce on it.
I'd like to pour it over it.
I wonder what mint sauce would be like?
Bon appétit!
Mmmm!
Delicious!
You know, the day I put mint sauce in.
It tastes so minty!
Maybe I'll try condensed milk.
The color of the condensed milk
It's not pure white.
It's really smooth.
It's very smooth condensed milk.
I wonder what it is...
Here we go...
Wow!
Delicious!
So sweet!
When I'm alone now, I really eat as fast as now!
I'm getting close to the last one.
Sad.
I'm sad, but
I can't stop because it's deliciousIt's so good, I can't stop.
The last bite!
Thank you for the food!
Wow, it was delicious!
Yes, today...
We had two drinks at two different restaurants!
Both of them were so delicious!
They were really good!
I'm not so much a...
I'm not a fan of refreshing shaved ice.
I really like shaved ice that is thicker and creamier
I'd like to know more about it.
There are so many of them.
I like rare cheese and not rare cheese.
I like cheese and bistachio.
And if it's seasonal...
I like cherries.
So, everyone who's watching this...
I'd love to hear your recommendations!
If you're here...
That's all for now.
Thank you very much for watching this episode.
Yes, and thank you for
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating
Thank you very much!
Wow, which way is it, this way?
This way?